Innocence dies. Abby doesn't.
Let Me In is a drama, horror, mystery film directed by Matt Reeves.
A bullied young boy befriends a young female vampire
who lives in secrecy with her guardian.
A remake of the movie “Let The Right One In” which was an adaptation of a book.
Owen, played by Kodi Smit-McPhee.
Abby, played by Chloë Grace Moretz.
The Father, played by Richard Jenkins.
The Policeman, played by Elias Koteas.
Virginia, played by Sasha Barrese.
Larry, played by Dylan Kenin.
Let Me In is a 2010 romantic horror film written and directed by Matt Reeves.
It is a remake of the 2008 Swedish film Let the Right One In, which was based
on the 2004 novel of the same name by John Ajvide Lindqvist.
The film stars Kodi Smit-McPhee, Chloë Grace Moretz,
Elias Koteas, and Richard Jenkins.
The plot follows a bullied 12-year-old boy who befriends and develops a romantic relationship
with a child vampire girl in Los Alamos, New Mexico, during the early 1980s.
Interest in producing an English-language version of Let the Right One In
began in 2007, shortly before the Swedish film was released.
In 2008, Hammer Films acquired the rights for the English adaptation and initially offered Tomas
Alfredson, the director of the original film, the opportunity to direct, which he declined.
Reeves was then signed to direct and write the screenplay.
Reeves made several changes for the English version, such as altering the setting
from Stockholm to Los Alamos and renaming the lead characters.
The film's producers stated that their intent was to keep the plot similar to
the original, yet make it more accessible to a wider audience.
Principal photography began in early November
2009 and concluded in January 2010.
Let Me In premiered at the 2010 Toronto International Film Festival on September 13, 2010, and was released in the United
States on October 1, by Overture Films, and in the United Kingdom on November 5, by Icon Film Distribution.
The film received positive reviews from critics, being placed on
several top ten lists of best films of the year.
Many critics noted it as a rare English-language remake which stayed true to the original,
while others criticized it for being too derivative of the Swedish film.
It earned $27 million worldwide against a production budget of $20 million.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
vampire, bullying, bully, child vampire.
The tone is dark and emotional and mind_bending.